[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Tests are ____ when they measure what they claim to measure, and reliable when they measure consistently.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise description of the aims and ____ of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Water is very ____ in many parts of North Africa.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The western end of the ____ route appears to have developed earlier than the eastern end, principally because of the development of the empires in the west.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These interviews are part of an ____ effort to discover our internal best practices and high points.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All students whose college/university will be forwarding tuition payments will need to contact the OSA to find out the ____ procedure.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to ____ an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A thought- provoking ____ suggests we should expect the extinction of intelligent life on Earth soon.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She is yet to master ____ verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I would be more prepared to ____ with the rules if I understood the reasons for them.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Howard has many chances to ____ into a better father and husband, but he fails to do so.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the ____ of a significant entity such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Lack of knowledge is not a suitable reason for failure to ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The department may ____ students of superior promise but deficient preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Stephen Krashen, a distinguished scholar and leading expert in the field of language acquisition, held an open forum to ____ his findings on five topics.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For my next step I would ____ to the students certain distinctions that might at first glance seem to be completely arbitrary or valueless.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Workers will ____ to where wages are higher.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The goal is to produce world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and ____ within the broad area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ criterion for successful teaching is the ability to interest the students.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was a very ____ test. Everyone got 100%.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief that scaling up HIV ____ counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a ____ consequence of having free will.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to ____ greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These poems ____ the poet's feeling of anger at the evil of war.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This home-school reading program should ____ the parent's role as teachers in their children's lives.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ the dimension of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Patience was not ____ in him, but he developed it under misfortune and opposition.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no place for those who have failed to ____ to better themselves with the opportunity afforded them.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Strauss said his health started to ____ and he was placed on the transplant recipient waiting list.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Production of oil and gas will ____ unless new reserves of oil and gas are discovered and developed.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There's no incentive to make an ____ if the teacher never gives you back your work.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to ____ the cost of complying with new requirements regarding data recording.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was only one ____ in a long struggle that did not come to a legal end until 1971.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too ____ a method of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can buy each ____ on the school supplies list from the bookstore.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have a ____ chance of passing your exams if you work really hard for the rest of the term.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This course traces the ancient ____ of the hero by reading selected works by authors such as Homer, Plutarch and Caesar,", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government can ____ that people eat more healthily but it cannot force them to do so.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To separate white light into its ____ colors with a prism and use an identical prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My father is going to ____ to Germany at the end of 2004.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dmitrieva and Kuptsova ____ an identical approach and understand culture as a realm of signs and meanings.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company's financial performance has been ____ affected by the rising cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the arteries is to transport oxygen around the body.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school tried to ____ the fact that one of its teachers had a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The prompt response of the Hu Jintao government has won ____ praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People who ____ from hay fever cannot have real flowers in their house. They have artificial ones instead.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Ruhrgebiet is a large ____ area in north west Germany.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It's no use trying to ____ me that your father speaks 10 languages. I just don't believe you.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was highly confidential and did not ____ his (personal) accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We can ____ that China is unlikely to put significant pressure on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such pressure.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She is unlikely to ____ above the rank of teacher helper; she is not very hard-working, and too often absent.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The death of Princess Diana was an ____ that shocked the whole world.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As the earthquake waves travel, they ____ all of the principles of other types of wave motion.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teachers are not universally in favour of the school's plan to introduce ____ working times.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any ____ of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There would seem a ____ chance that the United States, working with the United Nations, will lead a worldwide religious revival.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new policy means that faculty members can no longer ____ or modify grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The development of ____ communication protocols is a critical issue in today's age of pervasive communication.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Government scientists have found some red areas on the ____ of Jupiter, but they do not know yet what these signify.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents ____ by email, but they cannot insist on it.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Are you ____ sure that you gave me your homework?", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any mention of the type of action that the State would have taken against the ____ sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Tourists who visit a foreign city often employ a ____ to show them the most interesting things to see.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The angry shouts from demonstrators at the back of the hall did not ____ the politician in his speech.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company was in a very strong condition after winning a million dollar ____ to build its machines.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When the models incorporate the effects of pollution, they predict that rainfall will ____ even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In all such cases, we are happy to refund the ____ price and shipping charges once the prints are returned to us, at your expense, in good condition.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a ____ of living adequate for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Despite all the money spend on cancer research there is little ____ of a cure being found in the near future.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These interviews are part of an ____ effort to discover our internal best practices and high points.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war ____ Iraq is an appropriate occasion to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new rules will ____ to anyone who has come to Germany in the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most ____ advice that you can give your children is: Be yourself.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of all your hard work is an excellent exam score. Well done!", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to ____ the duties of the typical teaching job.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ its main attention to increasing business in the developing Chinese market.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same ____ could be a road to utter disaster.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Users want to maximize their access to ____ information, without losing sight of the amount of energy it takes them to get that information.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "First, you will need to ____ background information about all of the supporting questions.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to ____ the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Individuals should report the ____ to a faculty or staff member at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The final ____ presents the impact of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their effect on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people allege that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain ____ of its oil.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a vital ____ of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We did not ____ our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or field of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please ____ Einstein to your list of famous scientists.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If faculty ____ that a mental health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ problem facing the world this century is how to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "common"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The district cannot ____ the accuracy of the information or the appropriateness of any material that a student finds.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of equipment like a camera, it helps to have a ____ to look at.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Although nuclear power does not pollute the air, many people are against it because they ____ an accident or terrorist attack on a nuclear power station.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Israel and Korea are two countries that have ____ military service for their male citizens.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The head teacher could not ____ parents that there would be no increase in school fees.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to ____ patients to stop smoking. The habit is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Infinite power is so ____ and incomprehensible an idea that the mind of man must necessarily be bewildered in the contemplation of it.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a ____ or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have to ____ the amount of salt in the water.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free exercise of religion did not ____ an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on duty as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This survey is being used to gather information about the current level of frustration with computers and the ____ to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee ____ announced his intention to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very technical email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe ____ did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "University staff will ____ the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages instead of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's ____ was to increase sales by 20%. Due to the high cost of oil in the past year, it was not successful.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I conduct myself in a different ____ to different people.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people believe that harsh prison penalties for young criminals ____ natural justice.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These drug companies were ____ negligent in that they failed to warn consumers of the potential dangers associated with the use of their products.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to ____ the progress of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Weight loss is a constant ____ for many Americans.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to ____ how grammar and usage errors can interfere with meaning.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you do not have a particular title in mind, but wish to suggest that the library purchase more material on a specific subject, please ____ your name.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I ____ the way that animals are used in medical experiments.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The volume of business between Europe and Asia has ____ increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "too"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Homes were built and sold to families in need at no ____ and no interest.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you are applying from a country in which English is not the ____ language, you are required to submit evidence of English language proficiency.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A new ____ of skin replaces the damaged skin during healing.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If authors ____ there is a significant error in a published paper, they may correct their paper by submitting a short correction notice.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Today we will practise for the ____ test.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The study included a ____ of the main concepts of the authors' model on connecting children with nature and community.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people do not ____ a top engineering education with a liberal arts setting.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dinosaurs no longer ____ - they have been extinct for millions of years.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most of the families at our international school are here for a ____ of 2-3 years The ____ of the Earth's orbit around the sun is 365 days.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The 7 Harry Potter books have been published at an ____ of about 2-3 years.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ for other cultures is inherent in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some students may find it difficult to understand the ____ of democracy.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we want this plan to be a success, we need to ____ our resources very carefully.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ____ Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The headmaster called a meeting to try to ____ the dispute between the two teachers.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of equipment like a camera, it helps to have a ____ to look at.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most ____ function of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I am very ____ to help you after school if you have problems with your work.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government should pay particular attention to reducing unemployment ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This report draws on lessons learned from previous military deployments to consider strategies to ____ the health of troops in future deployments.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most serious ____ to implementing the Convention in Venezuela was clearly the poverty facing a large proportion of the population.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Lilly initiated a conversation with Smith in an attempt to resolve the conflict, but Smith did not wish to ____ the issues.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Her parents failed to ____ the bad influence of her new friends until it was too late.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The programme will include several ____ creative thinking techniques and this theme will recur in problem-solving mode in Part 2 of the programme.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Edwards ruled on the evidence presented and said Gary Edwards was not ____ to play.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The revolutionary ____ must come from those basic human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we want to maintain support for an open and ____ economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government decided to alter its ____ policy after three years of very slow growth.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The study showed that working 25 hours a week appeared to be the ____ where students' grades began to suffer.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A series of accidents and a mounting public ____ resulted in the government licensing of pilots and aircraft.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This international degree course has been ____ created for international students in their final stage of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to ____ students from families outside the usual sphere of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The reduction in personal tax is intended to ____ spending because people will have more money in their pockets.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very ____ email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was not a ____ that anybody in the world would consider wise.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will shrink ____ to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not circulate widely enough to ____ a revolution.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a ____ decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows ____ against the Germans.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has not been very successful in reducing teenage drinking, but it must ____ in its efforts.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Contrary to what you've been told by Courtney Love and the manipulated media reports, Kurt Cobain had no ____ for suicide.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "way"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new law will ____ unmarried mothers.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Each of these mechanisms has been investigated with a variety of blood sucking insects and the results clearly show that mosquitoes cannot ____ AidS.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are a few steps you can take to further ____ that construction activities do not damage the environment.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "____ments cannot govern without the broad assent of the people.", "Opt_1": "Enlarge", "Opt_2": "Govern", "Opt_3": "Presume", "Opt_4": "Prevent", "Answer": "Govern", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a ____ consideration in the purchase decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What is your ____ to paying higher taxes in order that more schools and hospitals can be built?", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My parents have decided to ____ me from eating in my room.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Every necessary ____ has been taken to provide up-to-date, accurate information in this website.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The university's plan to admit more students from poor backgrounds is an ____ that is not certain to succeed.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a ____ tax sheltered annuity program should contact their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is an ____ for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He reported that the presidential search committee has been formed and thanked some groups for forwarding ____ nominees.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His behaviour has not been very ____ since he returned from vacation.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In fact, most of the errors discussed on this site are ____ in the writing of privileged middle-class Americans.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Parents who are alcoholics often ____ their children both physically. and emotionally.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "About a quarter of the ____ and secondary students typically did not interact with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will notice an ____ that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you do not ____ the rules of the classroom, you will be sent to the headmaster.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The manager used the occasion of the opening of the new factory ____ to make a speech about future developments.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Each College or School should ____ the teaching of basic technology skills at the earliest level possible.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Bulgaria is to face a severe ____ of teachers within the next three years, education experts declared.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The solution must be practical. That is, it must be implementable with production - quality tools and technologies ____ today.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is a highly subjective ____ of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is typical to do market ____ before bringing out a new product.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you can ____ the problems you had with your last history project, I will be able to help you better with your current one.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students will ____ comprehensive analysis of several works and will compile a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "European democratic nation states have increasingly lost ____ over the conduct of their own economies.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although nuclear power does not pollute the air, many people are against it because they ____ an accident or terrorist attack on a nuclear power station.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Scientists are working very hard to find a ____ for oil. They hope that one day cars will not pollute the atmosphere.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teacher thought about the best opportunity to ____ that she was leaving to have a baby.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Children are able to ____ between reality and fantasy between the ages of 3 and 5, according to new research.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She has the ____ that she can pass the examinations without doing any work.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Very often, in the early summer, the hills are covered during the night by clouds, which do not always ____ until the sun has risen.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When traveling off-road, the car sensors must be able to ____ negative obstacles such as holes and ditches as well as positive ones such as trees or other cars.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The explanation for this extraordinary decision lies in the immediate ____ surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Too much ____ can trigger problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged period of time.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time ____ to the due date.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A significant obstacle to setting up a new business is the ____ amount of documentation that has to be completed.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial choice process, it is important to comprehend how migrants ____ space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The College will take no ____ for any actions taken by students who have been drinking, on or off campus.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was a loud argument in the cafeteria today. I had to ____ before it turned into a fight.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students who get in the athletic teams enjoy a high ____ in the school community.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nadeem has worked with FSU London since early 2004 as a permanent ____ of staff managing the Information Technology Systems.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic ____ is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made ____ through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I don't think that the school's ____ of the students caught smoking in the toilets was very fair.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "However, in those studies, he was unable to ____ the campaign's effectiveness in reaching the people of Uganda.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Eat less, ____ more: the formula for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police have not been able to establish a ____ for the brutal killing.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a rational decision but ____ one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He did not ____ to one set of religious beliefs and pioneered a new artistic style known today as symbolism.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teaching profession is usually not attractive to those are still pupils themselves. This choice of ____ is normally made much later.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We must reverse the ____ of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I ____ that problems at home are the reason for her poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "On the whole the great ____ of Canadian immigration of the past generation has been drawn from the English-speaking countries.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Scientists don't know how to predict drought a month or more in ____ for most locations.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The first section of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to ____ and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There are various ways that you can improve your English. Probably the best is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The search results are likely to include lots of hits that are not particularly ____ to your topic.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has failed to ____ a willingness to listen to people's concerns.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students receive feedback from the teacher on their performance on the interpretative ____ before they start on the next one.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Women are not the only ones in American society who feel ____ to achieve the perfect body.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a ____ analysis, thus it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The World Bank plans to ____ 50% more money to developing countries in the new year.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This interesting site offers the student of neuroscience access to an ____ amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For this task, instructors present a ____ of steps in a mixed order and students are asked to re-order the items into the correct sequence.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of effort invested in her language teaching she was not able to ____ grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The data is ambiguous as some analysts measure this ____ according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I really need one hundred percent concentration while performing my duties; I cannot be ____ messaging.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ task in the English classroom is to classify the parts of speech into nouns, adjectives, verbs, etc.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people are unwilling to address the ____ of global warming. They claim it is not happening.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I am often surprised by the ____ of some high school students. One of them yesterday did not know the name of the president of the USA.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's ____ and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government does not ____ an improvement in unemployment figures until the beginning of the new year.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The more powerful computers will continue to ____ all aspects of life.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please ____ your answer to a maximum of 100 words.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In an ____ group, each person can exert sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to set up a new computer lab, but the ____ would have been too high.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Teenage alcohol ____ is an enormous problem in some UK cities.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The union was not able to ____ all of its goals in this budget session.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you change your ____ or place of study, please amend your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ is planning to extend the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The points that you ____ should be proportional to the individual's contribution to your team for the quarter to date.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Standing on the table is certainly no way to ____ in the cafeteria!", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school will ____ its new vacation sports and study program at the beginning of next month.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people oppose the ban on smoking in ____ places, but the majority are in favour of it.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School needs to ____ its curriculum with that of German state schools.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In all cases, employers must offer ____ dates for a second-round interview if the date originally suggested is inconvenient.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no ____ of you having paid for the trip. Are you sure?", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you accept a housing assignment in the Summer Allocation and subsequently ____ it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you don't start working harder, we will ____ your right to leave the school at lunchtime.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The issue is of a ____ that cannot be solved by the school alone.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is set to ____ a heavy defeat in the vote to approve its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows ____ to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to recover it.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most students are neutral about the suggestion to ____ the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The result of such abuse was increased poverty in Russia and lost ____ in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can ____ your risk of getting a cold in the winter if you avoid others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The two scholars are impressed with the ____ audience of readers their blog drew after their first three postings on Dec. 5, 2004.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My ____ impression of him is that he is very intelligent and that his poor behaviour is because of boredom.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I refuse to ____ the idea that man is mere flotsam and jetsam in the river of life, unable to influence the unfolding events which surround him.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a regular basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To set up a practice test, I'd create a zero ____ test with questions from the year before in random order with random answers.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The information that you ____ in today's lesson will enable you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government predictably tried to ____ the report, and when it was released, attacked its author.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government will today ____ its annual report on crime statistics.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She has a ____ in one eye that makes it difficult for her to read from the board.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his ____ to correctly inform the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teaching ____ is under siege from an increasing number of social, economic and political factors, leading to large, unmanageable classrooms.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people suspect that the US government knew in ____ about the terrorist attack on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "C. S. Lewis tackled this issue head-on and offered some good advice that informs how we ____ our projects.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new law will ____ unmarried mothers.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is an excellent piece of work. You ____ your ideas very clearly.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ needs to consist of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If your students are not at the ____ you have planned for them in the middle of the quarter, you will need to investigate why this is so.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The manager used the ____ of the opening of the new factory block to make a speech about future developments.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Problems in school often ____ problems at home.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history major should demonstrate a significant ____ of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My family can't ____ a new house. They're so expensive in Germany.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a ____ component of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many athletes who take performance drugs risk serious, long-term ____ to their health.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a sharp ____ between Japan's fairly rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While I don't present this as absolutely the ultimate ____ that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Infinite power is so ____ and incomprehensible an idea that the mind of man must necessarily be bewildered in the contemplation of it.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A concise and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too ____ or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most students agree that teachers need ____ them on how much they have learned.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This survey is being used to gather information about the current level of frustration with computers and the ____ to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions ____ in that moment, in the detail of their description.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices ____ decreased until virtually zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The self-hatred that this ____ inflicted led the children to attempt to wash their skin white with scouring powder.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The student will have an opportunity to be re-examined if the ____ attempt was not satisfactory.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Cole Conservatory evolves from a Music Department with a long ____ of exceptional training for students from all backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to exert force in order to ____ peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An athlete may begin training at age 6 but cannot ____ until age 8.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The number of ____ warm nights and the length of heat waves will increase significantly over nearly all land areas across the globe.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ having a law if the police are not willing to enforce it.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is to be expected, of course, since natural selection is a natural process, and one cannot ____ moral principles from scientific findings.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has only had ____ success in reducing the number of unemployed people.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The unpleasant ____ in the computer lab is sure to occupy my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teachers ____ to improve student scores in standardized tests by doing 5 minutes practice at the start of every lesson.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies ____ multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He reminds us that ____ teaching methods are part of coming of age in the world of the Japanese performing arts.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not ____ of the property at any price.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of ____ issues, including the effect of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since the early 1990s, the number of smokers has continued to decrease but at the more gradual ____ of 5.2% annually.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Thorough cleaning must always ____ chemical disinfection of any equipment.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I've decided to ____ the idea of starting writing a book. I just don't have the time.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most people are ____ of the problem of global warming, but not many are willing to change the way they live.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government intends to ____ the information for itself. The public will not have access to it until the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A ____ for other cultures is inherent in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people used to believe that if cancer did not ____ within five years, a person was safe.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government will ____ its announcement until it has up-to-date information.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results are not at all satisfactory, and ____ discontent has arisen among the Indians on account of the issues that are being made.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "All around the school are small white boxes which can ____ smoke and set off the fire alarm.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students must ____ a working knowledge of a foreign language by translating a mathematical passage into English.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ 100 days until your final examination. It's time you started working.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This project will ____ in a major research essay of 2000 words.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I went on a long ____ last year. First I travelled to Japan, then I flew to Brazil. After that I sailed to California before coming home.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has no ____ to tell people how to live.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not ____ between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The sea froze over in the ____ cold.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mobile phones ____ parents to keep in contact with their children when they are out with their friends.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The students began to ____ when their teacher told them they would have a test on the last day before Christmas.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The union leaders promised to ____ for a longer lunch break for the employees.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is important to review language that reinforces the dominant culture's ____ to disability.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an ____ issue, but an internal one: the government failed to fulfill its duties.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many language teachers believe that their learners should use only ____ materials, not ones especially made for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Dr. Glick is an expert in ____ and public health nursing programs and issues.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are eligible for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not ____ Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a ____ possibility that she will lose her job unless she becomes more reliable.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to tell people how they should live and what they should spend their money on.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a deliberate ____ to conceal the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The referee of a football match can ____ the offside flag of his or her linesman.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When two atoms of hydrogen ____ with one of oxygen, then the result is H2O, water.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's ____ rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company's ____ plan was to close down only one of their factories. Because of continuing bad sales, however, they were forced to close three of them.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Today we will practise for the ____ test.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In this article, a novel way of teaching chemistry is presented that uses ____ music and chemical lyrics to educate.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My overall ____ of him since he joined the class is very positive.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In my ____ she is going to fail course unless she starts making more effort.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is never too late to ____ healthy habits! American Institute for Cancer Research.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How do we ____ the essential and perpetual problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Please ____ the missing information before submitting the form, otherwise it will be returned to you to complete.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to ____ a variety of materials to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What is the correct key ____ on a calculator for working out a percentage from a fraction?", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not all members of the Bush Administration have been telling the entire ____ about their dealing with Iraq.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Ruhrgebiet is a large urban ____ in north west Germany.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In many cases what was once an ____ is now taken for granted. Remarkable inventions, once assimilated into daily life, become routine.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to ____ his reply to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your grades will ____ to deteriorate unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Ask the candidate to ____ what they believe to have been their most significant challenges and accomplishments in their current job or a previous job.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Can someone please return this science ____ to the store cupboard?", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done ____ the comparison of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What is your ____ to paying higher taxes in order that more schools and hospitals can be built?", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable statistic and you should ____ ignore it.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This section of the GED web ____ provides several example questions from each part of the GED Tests.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its constant updating, people will be able to ____ new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is too early to make an accurate ____ of her problems in learning English.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is finding it difficult to break the cycle of poverty and ____ school performance.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a ____ consideration in the purchase decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government cannot afford to be ____ about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Food irradiation can be an important tool in the war ____ illness and death from foodborne diseases.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Problems in school often ____ problems at home.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After the attacks of September 11, 2001, Pat Cornell turned her ____ to detecting and preventing terrorism.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The principal made no ____ on the reasons for asking the student to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the school cafeteria, you can buy drinks of different sizes: small, ____ and large.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a ____ speed at all heights.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I ____ learning vocabulary as the single most important thing that ESL students should do.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ made no comment on the reasons for asking the student to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Buying a lunch ticket in ____ will entitle you to a free drink.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was a ____ thinker and an artist, albeit a rather unsuccessful one.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages benefit from a moderate ____ of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Furthermore, the text of the paragraph should correspond to the ____ sentence.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The fact that speech is likely to ____ in some violence or in destruction of property is not enough to justify its suppression.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning technique to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If there is any question whether the individual might have a physical problem, the mental health professional should ____ a complete examination.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Martin Luther King was killed ____ for insisting that America could not continue with people isolated on lonely islands of poverty.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Recent research shows ____ against African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to ____ how grammar and usage errors can interfere with meaning.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In his view, the Empire was less a place where England exerted ____ than where it lost command of its own identity.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not many people will change their habits or lifestyle ____ because a government minister tells them it's a good idea.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The report was designed to measure computer and Internet use ____ people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government reports a ____ decrease in unemployment in the last month.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The main ____ of the school is the teaching of science and mathematics.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a growing ____ to use the cell phone as the primary phone, without any need for landlines.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a very elementary problem. All the students were able to ____ it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Every 10 years the government carries out a ____ survey of all households in the country. This is called a census.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the ____ support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is the room where we store the science ____ ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Audio software can help students to record their spoken words describing an ____ concept or how to perform a computation.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Despite looking for Osama Bin Laden for many years, the USA still do not know his ____ location.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to ____ on your admissions application that you will have 24 credits completed at the time of attendance.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your final course grade will ____ on your grades in the 3 trimester exams.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not dispose of the ____ at any price.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Traveling really gives students a better ____ of the world.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Successful people ____ to have four underlying beliefs: I choose to succeed. I can succeed. I will succeed. I have succeeded.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Picasso's ____ to draw found expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was a very elementary problem. All the students were able to ____ it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My father is going to ____ to Germany at the end of 2004.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has taken the ____ decision to consult the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is an excellent report. The research is ____ and the writing clear.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In closing, I want to ____ that I know that our community is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The minister was unwilling to ____ on the changes in the price of oil in the next few months.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The weather ____ for tomorrow says that we can expect showers and a little weak sunshine.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some solutions ____ to improve the performance of these devices, but naturally there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar symbol of ____ to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people ____ pictures to the emails they send.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ new students otherwise one or two teachers will have to lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you move to London you will have to learn to ____ noise, crime and high prices.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My father's ____ in Germany will terminate at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company report did not do much to ____ the reasons for the fall in business in the previous year.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to ____ from the College.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government gave an ____ of its plans to change taxation. The full report will not be ready until next year.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "No wonder your computer doesn't work. You must ____ it to the monitor!", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The doctor had to ____ the x-rays carefully to find any signs of abnormality.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You may need to refer to the terms and ____ of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I think Kerry's biggest error, as a politician, is that he failed to ____ himself from Bush in any meaningful way.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The beauty of the telephone, and something that the telegraph lacked, was that it required no ____ to operate.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You should ____ a little more in class discussions. This will help to improve your spoken English.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The June 1992 Gender Equity Study found a significant ____ in salaries between men and women.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Russian is one of the ____ world languages and is spoken by over 250 million people.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He said that any art teacher who did not ____ students to ten thousand years of art was \"criminal.\"", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will not violate the personal ____ of co-workers and customers, and will respect their right to privacy.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is inevitable that any ____ society will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "History is filled with examples of ____ leaders who have suffered at the mercy of climate conditions that they failed to contemplate adequately.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some students see no ____ for learning German - especially if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our new system for handling lost property makes it possible for you to report the ____ of belongings via Internet, on the telephone or at the counter.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I am hoping that the students will ____ a non-native speaker onto the school council.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The faculty ____ cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In 1993 a student wrote an article critical of Martin Luther King. The response was ____ and negative.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new Smartboard in my classroom must ____ a lot of energy. I've already had to change the bulb 3 times.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many arguments would not ____ if people would define the words they use.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a ____ symbol of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The gap between Russia's dominant ____ power and our own inferior power could not be bridged overnight.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As the number of old people increases, so has the ____ that there is not enough money in the health system to take proper care of them.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time prior to the ____ date.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teacher should vary presentation styles and take into account ____ abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial choice process, it is important to comprehend how migrants ____ space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our teachers ____ the school's philosophy that only excellence is good enough.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The problems of drug-taking at the school ____ to get out of control.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows ____ to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to recover it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to ____ the scope of the problem.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His research helped establish that identical DNA sequences may behave differently depending on ____ and condition.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In closing, I want to assert that I know that our ____ is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families ____ the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The study of Growth and Development can help us to know a person more thoroughly and ____ be better doctors.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the ____ that urban life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many students look for ____ work between leaving school and starting university.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The committee needs to ____ of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Historically, there was ____ for crop and livestock losses, but the problem of estimating the damage and lack of funds for ____ programs has been significant.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you talk through a cloth it will ____ the sound of your voice.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Once Windows Movie Maker has opened, you will need to ____ the video clip that you would like to edit.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If submitted in other languages, an English version must ____ the submission.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The medical company decided to ____ production of its heart drug when it heard reports of the unexplained deaths of many people who had been taking it.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will lessen the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will lessen the ____ burden on society.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Politicians realize that they can't know everything, so they surround themselves with people who can ____ them.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Instead of getting involved in the affairs of other countries, the government should concentrate on its ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lucy has been formed by the West Indies; she still is deeply influenced, yet she would ____ and reject that heritage.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The remaining 40 percent said that they were not familiar with the ____ 'sustainable agriculture'.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher made the ____ decision to take her class out to the playground and finish the lesson there.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people think that the ____ way to stop people smoking is to raise the price of cigarettes sky-high.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This has been the province of scientists and engineers for many years and has only recently been considered a hot research ____ with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to invest a lot of effort over an extended ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government is heading into difficult ____ with its plans to ban smoking in all public places.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that ____ cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The substantial advantages of these close personal relationships far ____ the disadvantages of remaining small.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ when the angry parent said that he would contact his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was ____ poorly designed and therefore not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Musical ability is a ____ that some people are born with, but no-one succeeds as a musician without an enormous amount of practice.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For reasons that are not yet completely clear, practice and ____ usually diverge at this point.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last ____ of the flooded village was evacuated by a helicopter.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ is not a sufficient reward for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The writer was not careful when taking notes because he does not understand what plagiarism is, or because he is not ____ of what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has banned smoking in ____ all public places.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Bible laid down some rules for the humane treatment of slaves but did not ____ the practice.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company was fined a large ____ of money for attempting to violate pollution regulations.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each student's ____ was so varied that I was unable to isolate common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ resulted in a statistic that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Journalists were able to ____ the government's secret plan to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "From the quality of the writing I can only ____ that someone helped him. His work is usually nowhere near as good.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The comprehensive and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round ____ of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is easy to use the internet to ____ a lot of information. Whether it is of good quality is a different matter!", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He is universally considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to ____ key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you could ____ some of the unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors, your work would be even better.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You have one last opportunity to show that you can work hard and ____ properly. If you don't take it, you will be asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They will have to live without their family member for the rest of their life due to this terrible ____ of cancer and they will deserve to be compensated.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's a serious attack on any community's authority to develop and ____ housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used force to ____ food.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the notion that publishing houses lack sufficient diversity in both high and middle-level ____ members.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a resident of Indiana since at least December 31 of the ____ year.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ ignorance was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "All around the school are small white boxes which can ____ smoke and set off the fire alarm.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive ____ exam.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ was that starving the brain of sugar would kill marginally functioning brain cells, but the therapy was soon phased out because it was considered too dangerous.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The contributors examine the ____ of rivers on humans and, conversely, the ____ of humans on rivers.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The names of new products such as cars are not chosen at random. A large amount of ____ goes into choosing the most suitable name.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a ____ of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is suitable for ____s that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He did not ____ to one set of religious beliefs and pioneered a new artistic style known today as symbolism.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many a ____ that was once believed by everyone later proves to be false - e.g. that the sun goes around the earth.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government ____ wrote to confirm that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and ____ treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of predominantly White jurors.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The situation in Iraq continues to ____ the government's attention.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Before having a major surgical ____ patients must always consent.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Respect is not a commodity. You have to ____ it; you cannot buy it.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But please keep in mind that the Internet doesn't replace ____ counseling.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It seems that nothing will ____ her to get to class on time.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Where can I ____ about the teaching job I saw in the newspaper?", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is a particular ____ to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Insurance salesmen often ____ profits that they know are very unlikely.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a ____ for selection.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Previous ____ in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an advantage but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A verbal ____ is impossible to prove, and the organization will always maintain that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government can suggest that people eat more healthily but it cannot ____ them to do so.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of discrete issues, including the effect of shifting ____ patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her mother is a ____ visitor to the school. In fact she comes two or three times a week!", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Let's ____ the idea that you can actually teach critical thinking skills to primary school children.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the exact word to ____ an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I have no ____ to students wearing hats in the classroom, but many teachers do.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The supervisor will judge whether the paper is satisfactory, and ____ she or he should make sure the student has enough preparation.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is confident that the summer ____ cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge ____ regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I really need one hundred percent concentration while performing my duties; I cannot be ____ messaging.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding certain sentences that ____ common sense.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government will today publish its ____ report on crime statistics.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is the ____ of educators to prepare themselves carefully for each and every lesson.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Desdemona is ____ for much of the play and when she dies at the end, she takes the blame for her death.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The town council has been criticized for not providing enough ____ for young people in the town.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is often necessary to associate a ____ set of \"metadata\" with each data point in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How can the traditional classroom and the technology in it ____ deeper learning?", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His ____ is that if we don't cut taxes, then unemployment will rise.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting threaten to raise water levels and ____ flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of the school's drive to improve student eating habits is that far fewer plates of French fries are now sold in the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Can you please ____ how to make a table in Microsoft Word. I've read the instructions but don't understand them.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a result of the ____ amount of evidence for evolution accumulated over the last two centuries, we can safely conclude that evolution has occurred.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People today have become more conscious of their individual ____ to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Asia is our closest region and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and ____ culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This ____ that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, owe a huge ____ to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The course is predominantly concerned with the social relations of ____ that developed along with the major revolutionary currents of the eighteenth century.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Racism and prejudice continue to be a ____ problem in our country.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In some countries anyone caught taking drugs can expect a very ____ punishment.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In our ____ class on binary counting, we found a way to represent numbers using just two digits, 0 and 1.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Because of their behavior in protecting food sources, it is ____ unusual to see two hummingbirds spending time together.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people advocate government elections every four years ____ of every five as at present.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He will never be a good teacher. He has no ____ of the class.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Therefore he was unable to ____ that he was breaking new methodological ground.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no ____ without law, and no valid law or legal system when ____ is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher should vary presentation styles and take into ____ diverse abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In Germany most students have the chance to ____ practical experience in an office or factory, before deciding what job they would like to do.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The main ____ of a teacher is to teach.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power ____ failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When parents decide to send their children to a ____ -paying school, education becomes a commodity.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In Iraq the whole ____ of government was destroyed and had to be rebuilt.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents communicate by email, but they cannot ____ on it.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She lied to the ____ and cheated in her test, but because of her family situation, it was decided to allow her to stay.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to reject an offer of the ____ food.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A good way to guess the meaning of a new word is to ____ its context in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is heading into difficult ____ with its plans to ban smoking in all public places.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This report summarizes our ____ findings.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The basketball team was easily the strongest in the league. They were able to ____ all the other teams.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This certificate program is a series of fully online courses that will show you how to ____ and deliver a quality course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a chance to try out something different and immerse myself completely in another culture and it was a ____ I did not regret.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school tried to ____ the fact that one of its teachers had a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its constant updating, people will be able to ____ new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He said that any art teacher who did not ____ students to ten thousand years of art was \"criminal.\"", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not ____ us to abandon the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug abuse underlie many ____ health problems.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Being forced to speak before they are ready can ____ some adults' enjoyment and success in learning a language.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round cycle of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not ____ the level of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I understand her ____ to speak English in class. She has only just arrived at the school.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results are not at all satisfactory, and considerable discontent has arisen among the Indians on ____ of the issues that are being made.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its ____ or content.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "China is able to manufacture goods cheaply because ____ costs are low.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "result"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many students now ____ an electronic dictionary.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She accepted the arduous task of vice president, according to the papers, saying that she could not ____ the will of the people.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ resulted in a statistic that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the past 30 years, the ____ in Africa has continued to deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise ____ of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will encounter many difficulties but if you ____ in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Allies decided that Korea could not ____ itself after so many years of foreign rule.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not ____ a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All children below the age of 16 have the ____ to attend school.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "FLO plays the key role as an ____ for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Simply supplying more protein with alfalfa in the ration will reduce the need for purchased soybean meal and ____ in lower ration P.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people do not see the ____ of trying to save money when interest rates are so low.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is a very trivial example for demonstration purposes. However, the ____ is similar for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase ____ tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How people react to music is subjective. What ____s good to one person may ____ terrible to another.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we want to ____ support for an open and dynamic economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government expects to overcome resistance from some people to the prohibition of smoking in ____ places.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has passed laws to give equal rights to minority groups, but it can do nothing to ____ the prejudice that exists inside some people's heads.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally ____ bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My biggest ____ about the book is that Gruchy did not insert his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Very few companies can ____ cars of the quality of German makes such as BMW or Mercedes.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With his difficult family ____ it is not really surprising that he's having trouble in school.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Let's make it clear from the beginning that there is no one thing that you can do to ____ everyone, or even to ____ the same person every time.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In most countries of the world education is ____ for all children.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In order to self-correct your writing, you need to get an accurate ____ of your problems.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The manager has decided ____ a committee to investigate the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be ____ of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that ____ cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not ____ to 100% because many students were neutral on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a strong ____ between what the government promised to do and what it has actually achieved.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People have been trying for decades or maybe even centuries in an attempt to bring this ____ problem to an end.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has invited the ____ community to its Open Day.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They were unable to ____ the distribution of food supplies because of the deteriorating security situation.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students will ____ comprehensive analysis of several works and will compile a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The quality of your ideas and organization is much more important than the ____ of words you write.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy demand to ____ costs.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students post messages and ____ ideas through the bulletin board.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ for references must conform to the guidelines in the approved style manual.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Despite all the money spend on cancer research there is little ____ of a cure being found in the near future.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Chapter 6 gives a sketchy and rather incomplete ____ of molecular genetics.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She said that she will ____ to do better next trimester, but I'm not sure I believe her.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The book had arrived in stores by Sunday evening but store managers were under ____ instructions not to even open the boxes and put it on the shelves.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great ____ from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The course is ____ concerned with the social relations of power that developed along with the major revolutionary currents of the eighteenth century.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an image war, trying to ____ the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should not ____ the possibility that house prices will begin to fall.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to ____ the reviewer that the problem is worth investigation.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It took the Brazilian football player a little while to ____ to the speed and hardness of the English football league.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Every new car that is produced must ____ to standards that minimize pollution.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ is the most common teaching style at university. There is not so much question and answer as in schools.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Which activity are you going to ____ next time? - I think I'll try chess.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no anomaly but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly ____ to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our primary mission is to help you identify, plan for, and achieve your ____ goals.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She was able to ____ the Smartboard screen controls so that the presentation was visible to everyone.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an ____ solution to an ancient problem.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students are responsible for gathering all ____ necessary to support an appeal.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed assent of the student and signed ____ of the parent.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The terrorist plane crashing into the New York tower is an ____ that most people will never forget.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Conversely, rising wage rates often ____ workers to try to work fewer hours as they become rich enough to afford more leisure.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What is absent in your essay is any reference to the ____ of your ideas.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some students see no ____ for learning German - especially if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students needed to devote considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their ____ writing.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ when the angry parent said that he would contact his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we are to succeed in creating a true sense of citizenship in our students, we won't do so by offering an all-purpose, first-year ____ civics course.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Less than 10% of students who need basic skills ____ and don't get it survive in college.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The book is an educational and approachable reference in a difficult ____ of medicine where clinicians often feel uncertain.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university intend to make some changes in its admissions policy, but it cannot yet ____ what those changes will be.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ street demonstrations against its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He was highly confidential and did not ____ his (personal) accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an ____ meeting in order to share what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is possible to ____ cars so that they can be driven by people who have lost an arm or a leg.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to define any of these ____ terms, and yet I recognize some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The pictures presented aspects of the objects they could not ____ from the equations alone.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In ____ to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will ____ by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People with mental disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to ____ for them.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to exploit the resources that will allow them to ____ the future and avoid becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The headmaster's ____ is sure to provoke much discussion among teachers and students at the school.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not circulate widely enough to ____ a revolution.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a ____ against influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you change your ____ or place of study, please amend your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She rejects, thereby, traditional feminine ideals of marriage and ____ behavior.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Odland demonstrated the ____ to run a significant operation with a wide geographical spread.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people ____ to associate Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Parents who are alcoholics often ____ their children both physically. and emotionally.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Marat used his ____ ideas to arouse the people, and set himself apart.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ what a woman should do with her body.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will not have to ____ permission to publish if the purpose of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the notion that publishing houses ____ sufficient diversity in both high and middle-level staff members.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "From the outset of the gulf crisis, President George Bush stated that it was not his intention to ____ the Iraqi people.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein ____ the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not occupy much space.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The political system must not be allowed to ____ into unlimited majority rule, which could result in the erosion of individual liberty.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse ____ of education and research institutions vested in the common goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The format for references must ____ to the guidelines in the approved style manual.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new government proposals also ____ that all unemployed young people attend a three-week training course once a year.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He ____ failed to mention the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the ____ with a valid excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Each student must construct a Web ____ based upon his or her major research project.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Global warming will likely ____ big changes in California's coastal waters.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Less educated minority parents are more likely to manifest a ____ of involvement in their child's schooling.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most students are neutral about the suggestion to ____ the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an ____ war, trying to conceal the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school offers a free translation ____ to help families new to the school and to the country.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One enjoyable way to improve in English is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The book had arrived in stores by Sunday evening but store managers were under ____ instructions not to even open the boxes and put it on the shelves.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We have found that students are more likely to ____ a community health project if they join a team.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a massive ____ of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must ____ instruction for students.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You can ____ this book until the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Through appointments and legislation the President was able to ____ the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "One particular group of bacteria, the \"blue-green algae,\" have left a fossil ____ that extends far back into the Precambrian Era.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is too soon to ____ the success of the \"war on terror\".", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the ____ is sure to produce an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Racism and ____ continue to be a major problem in our country.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The book had arrived in ____s by Sunday evening but ____ managers were under strict instructions not to even open the boxes and put it on the shelves.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and external factors influencing the career development of first ____ Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government broadcast a warning about the dangers of terrorist ____ in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Obviously the result of many years of reading and reflection, this ____ study contains detailed summaries of dozens of works, both major and minor.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is possible to find the ____ of an object by measuring the amount of water that it displaces.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The problems of drug-taking at the school ____ to get out of control.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was ____ poorly designed and therefore not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At our 10th ____ symposium in late 2005, we posed this set of questions about Space Exploration: Who, What, When, Where, Why?", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of equipment like a camera, it helps to have a ____ to look at.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is clear that the Mid-Zambezi Project has failed in its ____ of controlling immigration.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She says she's not a very good pianist, but I know that the ____ is true and she's just being modest.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The detective was able to ____ from the size of the footprints that the thief was probably a woman or child.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is usually a close ____ between students of the same nationality at an international school.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We faced an ____ problem over 10 years ago and couldn't solve it then, either.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Not all members of the Bush Administration have been telling the entire ____ about their dealing with Iraq.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Smartboard is an excellent ____ for teaching language.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Begin your paper with a brief description of the storyline, or a brief ____ from it, that suggests or illustrates your thesis.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ the way that animals are used in medical experiments.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has set a clear limit on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the ____ every year.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students needed to devote considerable time to recognizing the three ____ tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student must also have a ____ address within the 22 South Texas county area.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Using a computer program makes it easier to ____ long pieces of writing.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students must ____ evidence of a competent reading knowledge of a language other than modern English.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Selecting the panelists is no easy task, and is subject to ____ lobbying.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "GeoRef is the most ____ single source of literature references concerning active volcanoes.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to protest about the government's decision to ____ the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You can ____ your work at any time prior to the due date.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government ____ a warning about the dangers of terrorist attack in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To ____ for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a generation efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Children are able to ____ between reality and fantasy between the ages of 3 and 5, according to new research.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may ____ an inaccurate or superficial analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, ____ is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Toscano, professor of history, talks about the war but refuses to let it ____ his curriculum.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The situation in Iraq continues to ____ the government's attention.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this article, a ____ way of teaching chemistry is presented that uses contemporary music and chemical lyrics to educate.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to ____ to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to support Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Government scientists have found some red areas on the ____ of Jupiter, but they do not know yet what these signify.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions ____ in that moment, in the detail of their description.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government does not ____ its citizens an explanation for every decision it makes.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors should give ____ advice and treatment to all patients, whether rich or poor.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to ____ on future developments, we need to consider the actual and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You should ____ a little more in class discussions. This will help to improve your spoken English.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Next year the school will ____ a policy of no smoking on campus for both teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of education and research institutions vested in the ____ goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally averse to this development.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some information is collected on our ____ by outside agencies in order to provide services to our visitors.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will gain no credit for work that has ____ been copied from the internet.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ____ Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A few years ago a robot was lowered to the seabed to ____ some objects from the wreck of the Titanic.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a ____ of Indiana since at least December 31 of the previous year.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Although two weeks are dedicated to its development at the end of the semester you should not ____ that this is enough time for the entire project.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids transmit ____ better than air.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student who had forgotten his homework was ____ that the teacher was absent that day.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government ministers ____ to treat people as children to be protected from all the ills of the world.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "That was not a very ____ thing to do.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government would like to reform the health ____ but the doctors are against their proposals.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam ____ very heavily on voluntary workers.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will descend by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a ____ of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is having difficulty trying to ____ the reasons for its change of policy.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She has a lot of ____ in tennis; in fact she's the best player in her grade!", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion ____ the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the ____ of the brain.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many undergraduates have little ____ in organizing tasks and making good use of time.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some people believe that smokers should not be ____ for free medical treatment.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Emma was ____ of these various and strongly held opinions, through professional periodicals.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The opening of the new sports block was the biggest ____ in the school's history.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school offers Latin but there is no demand for the subject ____ teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When parents decide to send their children to a ____ -paying school, education becomes a commodity.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Tai Chi is a ____ example of an art of self-defense that can be used effectively by both women and men.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student said that his dog had eaten his homework. The teacher did not believe him but could not ____ what he said.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is usually a close ____ between students of the same nationality at an international school.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Each of these mechanisms has been investigated with a variety of blood sucking insects and the results clearly show that mosquitoes cannot ____ AidS.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new manager needs time to ____ her own style of leadership.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not ____ a police order to halt and was shot.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A good way to guess the meaning of a new word is to examine its ____ in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We must trust the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a ____ consequence of having free will.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We wish to employ women who want to invent, create, and ____ the next generation of computers, and computing methodology.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government was fully aware of the ____ of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government claims that it invaded Iraq to bring democracy to that country. Many people, however, claim that this is not a ____ reason to go to war.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There are strict laws that govern the ____ in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One can fill a small book just describing the commonsense knowledge needed to solve an ____ problem like how to get to the airport.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a ____ analysis, thus it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The fact that she doesn't speak English did much to ____ the situation.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of the conflict remains very much in doubt.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These results ____ that substantial numbers of students attending the school are not attaining minimum levels of literacy and mathematical competency.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to ____ the dispute by the efforts of the local community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The North Viet Namese Army was not ____ enough to outflank southern forces.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised against the ____ questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I am often surprised by the ____ of some high school students. One of them yesterday did not know the name of the president of the USA.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Today women and men have the same ____ in western society. This wasn't always the case.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you do not ____ to the rules of the school, you will be asked to leave.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The rules of the school ____ that you must leave your mobile phone in your locker and not bring it to class.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Elders says that the U.S. must ____ its sick health care system.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "School need to base their curricula on the needs of the students who ____ them.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or extend the building's ____ infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The lack of available parking spaces is a significant ____ to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An error will ____ if this software is not installed on the user's machine.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The European Union attempts to align commercial and financial practices in its ____ countries.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's a bit surprising at first, how easy it is to measure such a huge ____ as the earth.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The campus will be closed except for needed emergency services and ____ work.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to fail to prepare properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "University staff will ____ the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages instead of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you want to have a more interesting style of presentation, ____ the speed and tone of your voice.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Schwarzenegger said he wanted to ____ junk food from school vending machines.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must ____ against the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This widespread ____ was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Not many people will change their habits or lifestyle ____ because a government minister tells them it's a good idea.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not willing to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's not that the mathematics is ____ difficult; the problem is comprehending the convoluted English.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Employees must have worked for the State for at least five years, and have a ____ record of sick leave usage and work performance.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Of course she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the ____ stage of learning English.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has made ____ progress towards its goal of reducing child poverty.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Are you ____ sure that you gave me your homework?", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was found that only 10 of these comparisons were acceptably consistent, meaning that their inconsistency ____ exceeded 35%.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I'm not sure that his parents realize the ____ of the problems he is having in school.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Since you have not attended class for the last seven weeks, I ____ that you are not interested in graduating.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next stage of the writing process is to ____ it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Before doing a longer piece of writing it is usually a good idea to make an outline to ____ your main ideas.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your ____ heart rate is a useful way of pacing yourself during exercise.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The blue whale may be extinct by the end of the century unless we do all we can to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I don't know how I always ____ to get such a good grade. I never work particularly hard.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to master problem-solving strategies that offer clear ____ solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The referee of a football match can ____ the offside flag of his or her linesman.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You have a ____ chance of passing your exams if you work really hard for the rest of the term.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The union leaders promised to ____ for a longer lunch break for the employees.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical ____ of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Hydrogen has the ____ to provide a clean, storable, transportable and renewable source of energy that can meet the need for power throughout the world.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For many persons these are not ____ concerns but profound and deep beliefs.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I don't believe you made a ____ effort to improve. Your grades certainly have not got better.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Turkish law requires foreign scholars to obtain ____ permission to carry out research at institutions in Turkey.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A frequent ____ in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is our ____ that the students were not given a fair hearing, and furthermore that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities interact so ____ as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If faculty suspect that a mental health problem may be the ____ of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Further analysis suggested that the ____ was worse for women than men.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school faces a real ____ in educating students from poor backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}]]